jeannie and adrian hit me up and we're
like that's bull
we did not realize that that was you
know happening amanda seals is getting
real about the reel spilling details on
which former co-hosts reached out after
the show snubbed her from their final
farewell episode there was never a show
that looked like us right and i'm so
grateful and i hope that we are not the
last you'll recall amanda co-hosted the
daytime show for six months back in 2020
[Applause]
so when she wasn't invited to be part of
the final episode and wasn't included in
any tributes amanda didn't hold back her
feelings so apparently the real
in their finale episode did promo
i am not featured in
this thumbnail and i am not featured in
the
uh farewell episode apparently
i'll have some things to say about that
and that's exactly what she did during
her appearance on the breakfast club
explaining why she thinks she deserved
recognition me leaving the real and me
verbalizing the reasons why i left the
real which i verbalized as because one
it wasn't feeding my soul because it was
being misrepresented at the end of the
day if you gonna do a retrospective of
the show over the years it's been on and
the hosts that have been on it it don't
matter what i say you were hosting the
show
i mean they kind of proved you right you
know what i mean
if you're saying that this show wasn't
good for my spirit because of x y and z
and then they purposely and
intentionally leave you out just like
which i have confirmed was the case duh
she also revealed she wasn't alone in
her thinking amanda says after the
finale aired both genie mai and adrian
houghton reached out to let her know
they're on her side jeannie and adrian
hit me up and we're like that's bull
we did not realize that that was you
know happening and we were gonna do it
live on instagram live but then our
schedules didn't line up and it was just
like you know
it's fine but
they they you know i talk to jeannie and
adrian all the time and ultimately
amanda makes it clear her beef is with
the show not her former co-hosts at the
time of her exit she said it was all
love between the ladies shout out to
jeannie shout out to tams shout out to
lonnie lance and shout out to adrian
what y'all don't understand is grown ma
grown women do grown women business
that's what y'all don't understand and
what i do with my business ain't got
nothing to do with them sisters and as
adrienne told et in 2020 one month into
amanda's gig as co-host she's got
nothing but respect for the comedian and
what she brings i've actually known
amanda the longest out of anybody else
out of anyone on the panel i've known
amanda since we both lived in new york
so um it was like a reconnecting yeah
like i had known her throughout all
these years and i was like
that's so dope like to have known her
from back then
still have that bond um i've always
loved who she is i've loved how
opinionated she is and that's what we
really what we love on the show is
having women that have strong opinions
and bring a different perspective
[Music]